# PHAN THI THU HUONG

Software Engineer Intern

DataHouseAsia Company

Binh Thuan, Hai Chau District, Da Nang City March 7. 2023

Dear Hiring team,

My name is Phan Thị Thu Hương. I am a sophomore at Passerelles Numériques Vietnam (PNV), which is a non-governmental organization in Vietnam. I am delighted to find out that DataHouseAsia Company is recruiting a software engineer intern through your website. I feel that my qualifications and experience make me suitable for this position. Therefore, I would like to apply for the position of Software Engineer Intern at your company.

During my study at PNV, I have absorbed and applied a lot of knowledge about Python, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL, BootStrap, and Github. I have done individual and group projects using these languages. In particular, I did a team project as a leader. I created a sales website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Mock API in that project. That project was rated well by my teacher and I got an 8.5. Besides, I am preparing to be taught ReacJS this March. Therefore, I guarantee that I will study seriously and apply that knowledge during the internship at the company. In addition, I regularly carry out projects to improve soft skills such as project management, teamwork, time management, and crowdfunding as a leader. I often communicate in English with volunteers from different countries around the world through PNV's English Club activities and the A Better Vietnam project.

I am sure that with my self-learning ability, perseverance, and will to progress, I will strive to become the best fit for this position. Moreover, I am a sociable, confident, responsible, and disciplined person at work, therefor I guarantee that I can complete the assigned work in the best possible way and bring much value to the company. I am convinced that serving as an intern at DataHouseAsia will be a critical step for me to apply my skills and knowledge while acquiring fundamental new tools in a challenging environment.

I am very much looking forward to having an interview with DataHouseAsia to demonstrate my competence as well as gain a deeper understanding of the company. Please find my CV enclosed for more information concerning my education and experience. If you need any further information, please contact me at 0814619859. I am available for an interview at your earliest convenience.

Thank you for considering my application. I look forward to hearing from you.

Yours sincerely,

Thu Hương



# PHAN THI THU HUONG

Software Engineer Intern

## Education

## **PASSERELLES NUMÉRIQUES VIETNAM** Bachelor Degree in Information Technology Oct 2021 - Oct 2024

# Experience

#### **FOOD PANDA SYSTEM**

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022 Programmer MySQL

- Designing database
- Coding queries
- · Creating tables and relationships

#### **TECH EQUIPMENT WEBSITE**

Nov 2022 - Dec 2022 Programmer

HTML, CSS & JavaScript

- Coding website interface
- Creating website effects
- Creating a responsive website

#### **SALES WEBSITE**

Oct 2022 - Nov 2022 Leader HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Mock API

- · Assigning tasks to teams
- Creating homepage
- Coding login and signup functions using mock API
- Supporting teammates to code admin page

### **Activities**

# SHARE HAPPINESS

#### Leader

- Managing and dividing tasks
- Fundraising to support the elderly

### Contact

0814619859



huong.phan24@student. passerellesnumeriques.org



101B Le Huu Trac, Da Nang



https://github.com/ thuhuong050903

# Technical skills

- Python
- HTML & CSS
- MySQL
- **JavaScript**
- PHP
- 00P

# Soft skills

- Teamwork
- Researching
- Presentation •
- Communication

# Languages

Vietnamese •

English

### Reference

Mr. Vo Cong Dinh

IT teacher



0905729707



dinh.cong@

passerellesnumeriques.org